https://www.usalliance.org/website-privacy-policy

ALERT: Online Banking is currently unavailable for maintenance, Monday, December 7 at 9:30pm. Account access will be available through Mobile Banking via the USALLIANCE Mobile App. We apologize for any inconvenience.
ATM / Branch Locator
Routing Number: 221981063
Blog
Make a Payment
Financial Education
Application Status/Upload
Online Banking Sign In
Secure Sign-In ID:
Secure Sign-In
Forgot your password?
Enroll | Security Center | Help
Making a Payment? Enter Payment Center
Bank
View All Banking Products
Compare Credit Cards
View Savings Rates
Checking Accounts
MyLife Checking
View Certificate Rates
Individual Retirement Accounts (IRA)
Certificate Accounts
Retirement Central
Protect
View All Insurance Products
Overdraft Protection
Overdraft Privilege
Vehicle Insurance
Guaranteed Asset Protection (GAP)
Mechanical Breakdown Protection
Health Insurance
Telehealth
Long-Term Care Insurance
Personal Insurance
Homeowners Insurance
Life Insurance
Pet Insurance
View Certificate Rates
Individual Retirement Accounts (IRA)
Certificate Accounts
Retirement Central
Protect
Back
View All Insurance Products
Overdraft Protection
Overdraft Privilege
Vehicle Insurance
Guaranteed Asset Protection (GAP)
Mechanical Breakdown Protection
Health Insurance
Telehealth
Long-Term Care Insurance
Personal Insurance
Homeowners Insurance
Life Insurance
Pet Insurance
Sign In
Secure Sign-In ID:
Forgot your password?
Enroll | Security Center | Help
Making a Payment? Enter Payment Center
USALLIANCE
Website Privacy Policy
Last Updated: July 13, 2015
Please Read Carefully
USALLIANCE Federal Credit Union, also known as USALLIANCE Financial ("USALLIANCE Financial," "us," "we," or "our") is committed to protecting the privacy of the users ("user", "you" or "your") of the consumer facing website (or any other sites linking to this policy) operated by it (collectively, the "Site") and when you engage with us through social media sites. USALLIANCE Financial's Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the non-personal information you provide to us and in making informed decisions when using our consumer facing website. This Privacy Policy applies to the Site and governs data collection and usage at the Site. The United States has data protection laws that may not be consistent with those of other countries. By accessing, browsing and/or using the Site, including all content, software, functions, services, materials and information made available on or accessed through the Site, you acknowledge that you have read, understood and agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy.
Cookies and Other Technologies
We and our authorized Service Providers (as that term is defined below) employ cookies, widgets, clear gifs/web beacons, pixel tags, log files and/or other technologies to store, track, determine, and authenticate information about the users of our Site. Such information allows us to analyze site usage and user demographics, interests and behavior to better understand our users and improve our Site and user experience.
Cookies are a feature of web browser software that allows web servers to recognize the computer used to access a web site. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by a user’s device. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on a web page to simplify subsequent interactions with that web site by the same user or to use the information to streamline the user's transactions on related web pages. Most web browsers and devices automatically accept cookies, but you can change your browser to prevent it from accepting cookies. If you set your browser to reject cookies, you may still use the Site, but your ability to use some areas and features/functions of the Site may be limited.
Clear gifs/web beacons are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of users as well as to determine if email sent by us to subscribers have been opened, clicked, or had any action taken. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's device, clear gifs/web beacons are embedded invisibly on web pages. Clear gifs/web beacons and auditing software are used to track page views and entry and exit points to and from the Site.
Targeting cookies are used when you click on the "Share," "Like," "Facebook" or "Tweet" buttons that may be found on certain web pages of our Site and are linked to services provided by third parties. Such third parties subsequently may use information about your visit to target advertising to you on their web sites. They also may share such information with others, including advertising agencies. We do not control the setting of these cookies nor the cookie data sent by your browser to the third parties in order to associate the buttons to your accounts with those parties, which data is not accessible to us. We encourage you to check with the third party web sites concerned for more information about their cookies and how to control them.
We may use clear gifs/web beacons and/or similar technologies to better tailor, manage, place and/or display our own and/or third-parties' advertisements/banner ads and/or content on the Site. We may use similar technology to tailor, manage, place and/or display advertisements/banner ads that are reflective of a user's interests based on that user's browsing behavior. These technologies may be in use on a number of web pages across the Site. When you access these pages, a non-identifiable notice of that visit is generated, which may be processed by us or by our Service Providers. These clear gifs/web beacons usually work in conjunction with cookies. If you do not want your cookie information to be associated with your visits to these pages, you can set your browser to reject cookies. If you set your browser to reject cookies, gifs/web beacons and other technologies will still detect visits to these pages, but the notices they generate cannot be associated with other non-identifiable cookie information and are disregarded.
To support our information provision and engagement, we may embed photos and video content from web sites such as YouTube, Vimeo, Flickr and others. As a result, when you visit a page on our Site with content embedded from, for example, YouTube, you may be presented with cookies from this third party web site. We do not control the dissemination of these cookies. We encourage you to check with the third party web sites concerned for more information about their cookies and how to control them.
The Site may use the use of analytics, Adwords or other similar advertising partners. These sites utilize cookies and user based information to help us to analyze how users use the Site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the Site (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by sites such as, but not inclusively, Google, Bing, and Yahoo on servers in the United States and/or in other countries. These sites such as Google or Adwords will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Site, compiling reports on web site activity for us and providing other services relating to web site activity and Internet usage. The other Site’s may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on their behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google but may remarket or advertise to you based on your demographics or preferences. As set forth above, you may reject cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. If you choose to do so, however, you may not be able to use certain areas and features/functions of the Site. By using this Site, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
Types of Information Collected
Through the use of cookies, clear gifs/web beacons and other technologies, we and our authorized Service Providers automatically track and collect certain anonymous information about our Site traffic (collectively "Traffic Data") and store it in log files. Traffic Data includes, but is not limited to, Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, domain name, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, advertising/promotional campaign from which the user linked to the Site, operating system and/or platform, date/time stamp, geo-location, number of page views, page or section accesses, ads viewed and interacted with, clickstream data, and ebook downloads. Traffic Data is used by us and/or our Service Providers to track users' engagement and movements around the Site, to analyze trends, to administer the Site, to assist us in designing and arranging our web pages in the user-friendliest manner and to continually improve our Site to better meet the needs of users. We may place and/or display advertisements/banner ads on the Site that originate from outside advertisers and other third parties. If you click on and/or view these ads, the advertisers/third parties may assign cookies and automatically track and collect certain anonymous information. We do not control these cookies, nor are we responsible for any marketing or other use of your information by these outside advertisers or other third parties.
We also may use third-party advertising companies to place and/or display advertisements/banner ads when you visit the Site. These companies may assign cookies and automatically track, collect and use certain anonymous information about your visits to the Site and other web sites in order to provide advertisements/banner ads about goods and/or services that may be of interest to you. We do not control these cookies, nor are we responsible for any marketing or other use of your information by these third-party advertising companies. In order for you to access certain areas and functions/features of the Site, register with USALLIANCE Financial and/or participate in certain online activities (such as participating in our programs, surveys and/or promotions (e.g., sweepstakes and contests), posting to blogs, bulletin boards, reviews, and submitting online comments) we may ask you to establish certain login information and/or otherwise provide us with information that personally identifies you, such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address and home and/or business telephone numbers ("Personal Information").
If you communicate with us by e-mail or otherwise complete online forms or the like on any USALLIANCE Financial-operated and/or sponsored web site and/or through USALLIANCE Financial- managed social media accounts information provided in such communication may be collected as Personal Information. In addition, if you engage with us through social media web sites or through features on any of the web sites operated by us that integrate with social media sites, you may allow us to have access to certain Personal Information and other information from your social media account (e.g., name, e-mail address, photo, gender, birthday, city, the posts or the 'likes' you make).
You may choose not to provide us with any Personal Information. In such an event, you can still access and use much of the Site. You, however, will not be able to access or use those areas of the Site or participate in online activities that require your Personal Information.
Participation in online activities at the Site may be subject to additional terms, conditions and notices and such activities shall be governed by such terms, conditions and notices. In the event of any conflict, such additional or different terms, conditions and notices will prevail over this Privacy Policy.
Uses and Sharing of Information Collected
Except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, we will keep your Personal Information private and will not share it with third parties without your consent, unless such disclosure is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on us; (b) provide you the products, services and/or information that you may have requested; (c) protect our rights or property; (d) enforce our rights; (e) protect the interests of users of the Site, other than you, or any other person; (f) operate or conduct maintenance and repair of our equipment; (g) detect, prevent and/or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues; and/or (h) otherwise comply with applicable laws.
In general, we will use Personal Information only for the purpose for which such information was provided to us. We may also use Personal Information (a) to verify the information you provided to us; (b) to provide you with the information that you have requested; (c) to respond to your inquiries; (d) to contact you when necessary; and (e) to display, provide or send you information about us, including information related to our products, services, programs or promotional activities, or about third party products, services, programs or promotional activities, that may be of interest to you. In the case of third party products, services, programs or promotional activities, your Personal Information is not transferred to the third party. If you sign up/subscribe to our electronic newsletter(s), we will use your name and e-mail address to send the newsletter(s) to you.
We may share Personal Information with our affiliates or subsidiaries. We may also share your Personal Information with third parties that provide services to USALLIANCE Financial ("Service Providers") (including handling and delivering of e-mail communications and electronic newsletter(s), user submitted information processing and/or storage, user submitted complaint processing and handling, web analytic services, e-mail analytic services, web marketing, and web site hosting and other application services) as reasonably necessary for them to provide said services. Service Providers of USALLIANCE Financial who have access to personal information, however, are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy and not to use it for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for USALLIANCE Financial.
We may use traffic, behavioral, and demographic data to analyze trends, administer the Site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
We may provide this data and/or other aggregate non-personally identifying information to third parties.
If you have registered with us, interact on our affiliated social media sites, or sign up/subscribe to our email(s) and click on a link contained in an e-mail sent by us, we may link traffic, behavioral, and demographic data to your user name, email, and to your Personal Information solely for our own business purposes and use, including to customize and tailor your experience on our Site, to serve, remarket, and/or display specific advertisements/banner ads and/or content during or after you visit the Site, and to send you information about us, including information related to our products, services, programs or promotional activities, or about third party products, services, programs or promotional activities, that may be of interest to you based on your usage of and behavior on the Site.
Notwithstanding the foregoing, we may transfer or assign information concerning the Site and your use of the Site, including without limitation, personal information, to third parties, as a result of a merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation of USALLIANCE Financial.
Promotions
When you enter a promotion such as a sweepstakes or a contest hosted and/or sponsored/co-sponsored by USALLIANCE Financial, we ask for Personal Information. If prior to entering a promotion, you had opted to become a Registered User for purposes of facilitating your provision of certain information (including certain Personal Information) required in order to enter promotions hosted and/or sponsored/co-sponsored by USALLIANCE Financial, when entering the promotion online, the fields on the online entry form pertaining to your contact information or other Personal Information requested may be automatically populated using the information from your existing account to the extent available. You still, however, will be required to confirm the accuracy and completeness of such information at the time of entry.
We may contact you in connection with a particular promotion in order to update you of your status, administer the promotion, let you know that a promotion has ended, and for other purposes related to the promotion.
Promotions that are hosted on the Site may be sponsored by USALLIANCE Financial, sponsored by a third party, or may be co-sponsored by USALLIANCE Financial and another party or parties. Some or all of the data collected during a promotion may be shared with the sponsor(s) or companies indicated on the Official Rules and/or entry form.
Promotions that are hosted by a third party on a web site other than our Site may collect and use information alone or in conjunction with USALLIANCE Financial. The nature of this information sharing policy will be indicated on the Official Rules and/or entry form. If information is collected and used by a third party, you will need to see their Privacy Policy to understand how that information may be used.
Some of our promotions may use cookies, clear gifs/web beacons, log files and/or other technologies in order to track your progress and number of entries.
When you participate in a promotion hosted and/or sponsored/co-sponsored by USALLIANCE Financial, you are subject to the Official Rules of that promotion. To the extent provided in the Official Rules, information contained in a participant's entry also may be subject to and may be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In the event of any conflict between the Official Rules and this Privacy Policy, to the extent it applies, the terms of the Official Rules will control.
Opt-Out/Discontinue
If you sign up/subscribe to our electronic messages and you no longer wish to receive our emails, you may also unsubscribe by following the unsubscribe link located within each e-mail communication.
Links
The Site contains links to third party web sites. These links are provided solely as a convenience to you. If you access those links, you will leave the Site. USALLIANCE Financial does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from USALLIANCE Financial's practices. USALLIANCE Financial is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of linked third party sites and does not make any warranty or representation regarding the content or accuracy of materials on such sites. USALLIANCE Financial does not make any warranty or representation regarding, nor does it endorse, any linked third party web sites or the information appearing thereon or any of the products or services described thereon. The personal information you choose to provide or that is collected by these third parties is not covered by our Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy of any third party before submitting your personal information. If you decide to access linked third party web sites, you do so at your own risk.
Public or Interactive Areas of the Site
Information that you post on or through the public or interactive areas of the Site (such as by filling out a comment box, submitting a product review, and/or using our blog, and other outlets, generally is accessible to others. Any personal information you post there can be read, collected, and/or used by other users of these forums, and may result in unsolicited messages or other contact from others. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to post on or through the public or interactive areas of the Site.
If you post information when you interact with us through social media sites, depending on your privacy settings, this information may become public on the Internet. You may be able to control what information you share through privacy settings available on some social media sites. For more information about how you may be able to customize your privacy settings and how third party social media sites handle your personally identifiable information, please refer to their privacy help guides, privacy statements, terms of use and/or similar materials.
Notification of Changes
We may change our Privacy Policy at any time by updating this posting. Changes to our Privacy Policy will be effective when posted.
Policies for Individuals Under 13 Years of Age
We are committed to protecting the on-line privacy of children. In accordance with the Children's On-line Privacy Protection Act, we do not, and will not, knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that personally identifiable information has been collected from individuals under the age of 13, we promptly will take all reasonable steps to delete such information.
Acceptance of Privacy Policy
By using the Site, you signify your assent to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or any questions about the security at our Site, you can contact us through our Contact Us page.
USALLIANCE Financial
411 Theodore Fremd Ave.
Suite 350
Rye, NY 10580-1426
ABA Routing Number:
221981063
Contact Us
+1 (800) 431-2754
memberservices@usalliance.org
Notice: Do not include account numbers, social security numbers, personal identification numbers (PINs), passwords, or other confidential information in your e-mail messages.
Accounts
Bank
Borrow
Invest
Protect
eServices
Company
Why USALLIANCE
About USALLIANCE
USALLIANCE Financial is a full-service credit union that offers a wide range of banking services. We develop and implement custom-made, secure, and innovative products for many great organizations, in addition to our 120,000+ members worldwide.
©2020 USALLIANCE Federal Credit Union. All rights reserved.
Privacy Policy | Website Privacy Policy | Terms of Use
USAlliance Federal Credit Union d/b/a USALLIANCE Financial
NMLS #562301 Equal Housing Lender
*APR = Annual Percentage Rate | APY = Annual Percentage Yield
Federally Insured by NCUA
You are about to enter a website hosted by an organization separate from USALLIANCE. Privacy and security policies of USALLIANCE will not apply once you leave our site. We encourage you to read and evaluate the privacy policy and level of security of any site you visit when you enter the site. While we strive to only link you to companies and organizations that we feel offer useful information, USALLIANCE does not directly support nor guarantee claims made by these sites.
I Understand
Cancel
